MOBILE

402.990.6076

EMAIL

hello@angelasnodgrass.com

GITHUB

github.com/afausch

Angela Snodgrass

I am a junior front-end web developer with over 15 years of marketing experience. I am seeking entry-level opportunities that will allow me to collaborate with and learn from experienced web developers. I am passionate about design and programming and am eager to grow more as a developer.

SKILLS







Interpersonal



Project Management



Presentation



Collaborative



Creative



Adaptable



Self-Motivated



Analytical



Organizational



Detail Oriented



Dedicated

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5

PACE

- CSS3
- Git
- JavaScript GitHub
- jQuery WordPress
- Bootstrap
- **Brackets**

EDUCATION

Interface Web School, Omaha, NE

Web Foundations: 11-Week Front-End Web Development Program

Nebraska Wesleyan University, Lincoln, NE

B.A. Communications, Minors Business Administration & Theatre Arts

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2016 - Present

Contractor at KOVUS, a market research and digital product company in Omaha, Nebraska, gaining valuable experience in UX/UI design, user research and testing. and front-end web development.

Developing and implementing a communication plan for Great Call Coach, a startup company that provides football coaches with the technology and analytics to be more efficient.

Graduated from Interface Web School front-end web development program in March 2016.

Kiewit Corporation Omaha, NE Jan 2013 - Jan 2016

Employee Relations Specialist

Managed internal case management system, internal webpages, and internal and external correspondence. Prepared reports, presentations, metrics, and trend analyses. Coordinated internal postings of requisite state and federal compliance posters. Facilitated outreach programs and engagement activities.

Immigration Specialist

Prepared immigration petitions, primarily involving Canadian applications. Actively engaged with Kiewit's talent to ensure proper collection of relevant documents and information to secure a foreign work permit.

Legal Administrative Assistant

Provided administrative support to three in-house attorneys. Maintained legal case management system, composed legal correspondence, processed invoices, coordinated travel, and reconciled expenses.

Contractor, HR Assistant

Assisted with end of year filing, conducted candidate experience research, created Social Media Press Kits, assisted with event coordination, and compiled research for online corporate branding strategies.

TD Ameritrade Omaha, NE Sep 2012 – Dec 2012 Contractor, Transfer Analyst

Reviewed and analyzed transfer forms to ensure completeness and compliance with industry rules. Facilitated accurate settling of securities transactions with brokers by using various depositories.

ConAgra Foods Omaha, NE Nov 2011 – Jul 2012 **Customer Supply Chain Specialist**

Responsible for the Customer Service and Order Management functions of convenient store customers.

Contractor, Recruiting Coordinator

Maintained applicant tracking system, posted job opportunities, tracked applications, drafted offer letters, submitted background reports, and coordinated pre-employment drug screens.

Software Engineering Services Omaha, NE Jun 2011 – Nov 2011 Contractor, HR Manager

Identified staff vacancies and recruited, interviewed, and placed qualified candidates. Developed candidate database and attended career fairs.

Oriental Trading Company Omaha, NE Sep 2009 – Apr 2011 Creative Coordinator

Ascertained pertinent marketing and merchandising information through frequent and consistent communication with merchandising, public relations, and marketing. Directed the timely completion of projects.

Email Marketing Specialist

Oversaw all aspects of the marketing campaign process including planning, building, testing, and analysis. Analyzed campaign results and implemented changes. Developed and implemented new campaign ideas and promotion strategies. Optimized targeting, acquisition, and retention opportunities.

THT Designs Omaha, NE Dec 2006 – Sep 2009 Marketing Supervisor

Planned, tested, and executed direct marketing strategies and profitability across all non-catalog channels. Oversaw websites to expand online sales and enhance brand image. Managed changes to websites including featured products, overall content, navigation, and functionality.

Marketing Specialist

Conducted all aspects of budgeting, campaign planning and research in order to develop successful marketing campaigns. Worked with internal departments and outside vendors to successfully implement campaigns. Pursued editorial opportunities and managed space ads.

Key Accounts Sales Assistant

Performed order entry, order writing, coordinated freight and order logistics.